- [Instructor] Now let's add the code to the PlayerSingle.
So, the first thing we're going to do,
we're going to make sure that we pass the currentPlayer state
to the PlayerSingle.
So as you can see in the constructor, we have an object
that's called currentPlayer.
And as we click on the players, we're going to pass
who is this player to the currentPlayer
and then pass this down to the PlayerSingle.
So let's go ahead and make sure
that we are passing this prop.
So, we're going to do player
and we're going to pass this.state/currentPlayer like so.
Make sure you do dot and not forward slash.
Okay, we're going to save this
and then we're going to close this guy here,
close the App.jsx.
And now, we're going to go in the PlayerSingle
and do a lot of code here.
All right, so let's go and open PlayerSingle.
I'm going to close my explorer
and I'm going to start working
on this specific Player Single.
So, I'm going to remove the title here
and I'm going to start with a className of row.
And inside that className of row,
we're going to have another div
with a className of column s12.
So we're going to take full advantage of the width
of that particular row.
And then inside of that row, we're going to have a card.
So, let's go ahead and create a new div, className of card.
And these are all styles from Materialize,
the library that we installed earlier.
Another div with a className of card-image.
And inside of that card-image, we're going to have
an image first with a source of soccer.jpeg,
and while we're on the subject, I'm going to grab that image
from the resources.
So, if we go here in the Exercise Files,
you're going to have in the resources this image here.
So, we're going to copy that image
and we're going to put it in our project frontend
in public right here like so.
And you can delete the vite if you want while we're here.
Okay, and now that image is going to be available.
And remember when you do an image, you need to add an alt,
so Soccer Image if you want.
You can call it anything you want here.
And we're going to close out that tag.
And then we're going to have a span
for the title of the image.
So that span, which will have a className of card-title,
and you want to make sure you pass props
because we've passed from the state,
the currentPlayer, so we need to be able to use it now
from our props.
We're going to have player.firstName
and props.layer.lastName.
And again, if you're not sure what we've done,
you can go in here and you can go to the app
and you can take a look.
So we passed this prop as player.
So the currentPlayer is passed as a prop, as player
and not currentPlayer,
so that might be the confusion for some of you.
So if that's the case, you see what I've done here.
So, this is accurate here.
Okay, so now we have our span here. We're good to go.
Now we need to go out of that card-image
and create a new div.
And that new div is going to be className="card-content".
And then inside of that card-content,
we're going to have a few things.
So, the first one is going to be a p tag,
which we'll do Phone, and then we're going to have
props.player.phone, then dash Email.
So basically, we're building out all the data
that we have available inside of our player.
So as you can remember, when we set our schema,
we have several things that we have access to.
Then we're going to add another line.
So, another p tag on this area.
We're going to add Strength, and I'm going to copy and paste
to just speed up the typing.
So, props.
On this one, we're going to go for strength,
and then we're going to do Endurance.
And then this one, we're going to do endurance.
And then you can continue with all the skill sets
that we added to the database.
So, I'm not going to do all of 'em,
but you could do every single one of 'em.
So, it's basically a repeat of all the skill sets
that we added into the database.
You can do props, agility, and so on, so forth.
So, feel free to continue and finish this off if you want.
So I'm just going to complete the SinglePlayer
by doing card-action.
And the card-action is going to be Team and team.
Okay?
So that's pretty much what we need to do
for the PlayerSingle, so I'm going to save this
and we're going to continue finishing our application
in the next few videos.